Finding Aid for Central Michigan University. Multicultural Education Center Collection
Clarke Historical Library
- Central Michigan University. Multicultural Education Center Collection
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 4, Multicultural and Diversity Education Council,1990-2005 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 4, News Clippings (copies) Native American Symbols as Mascots (copies),1988-2005 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 4, Presidential Advisory Committee on Anishnaabe Education Through Art,2001 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report: Chippewas as University Symbol,1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report: Department of Religion, Nickname Issue,1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report: Department of Religion, Nickname Issue,1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report: Presidential Advisory Committee on “Chippewas” as Symbol,1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report: Public Agenda, “A Qualitative Study Exploring How Indians and Non-Indians Think About Each Other,2007 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report: Symbol Advisory Committee,1990 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report to the President: Chippewa Nickname,2000 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Report to the President: Student Opinion Survey, Chippewa Nickname,2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Saginaw Chippewa Indian Tribe, Tribal Council on the Use of Chippewa Symbol, Booklets,1988-2003 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Statement on the Chippewa Nickname,undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Steering Committee: Chippewa Nickname Issue,2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 5, Student Government Association, Academic Senate, Chippewa Nickname Issue,1989 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 6, VHS Videos: Campus Forums on Diversity, #1 Accommodating Diverse Backgrounds in Class, Student Panel,2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 6, VHS Videos: Campus Forums on Diversity, #2 Accommodating Diverse Backgrounds in Class, Student Panel (continued),2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 6, VHS Videos: Campus Forums on Diversity, #3 Nes Mnumzana,2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 6, VHS Videos: Campus Forums on Diversity, #4 Mike Petoski and Student Inter (tape 1 of 2) [Note: no tape 2 is in the collection],2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Addition Acc# 73681, Box 6, Cassette Tape: Shirley Brauker,1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Addition Acc# 76658, Box 1, VHS Videos: The Legal (Pre-Employment) Interview, 1984; Handicappers Rights, 1988,1984, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Addition Acc# 76658, Box 1, VHS Videos: Cultural Diversity at CMU, [1988]; Sexual Issues in the University, 1989,[1988]-1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Addition Acc# 76658, Box 1, VHS Videos: Marshall Rose on Whites in Black History, 1989; Have We Finally Arrived at Educational Equity Forum, 1990,1989-1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Addition Acc# 76658, Box 1, VHS Videos: Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. Freedom March and Commemorative Program, 1991; Affirmative Action Annual Think Take, Tape 1, 1991,1991 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Addition Acc# 76658, Box 1, VHS Videos: Affirmative Action Annual Think Take, Tape 2, 1991; Dr. Lloyd Elm, Lincoln Address, 1993,1991, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 5)